{
    "subject": "resource/John_Gardner_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Boysie_Oakes",
    "human_readable": "John Gardner (British writer) wrote 'Boysie Oakes'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8945407867431641,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'Boysie Oakes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6890680193901062,
            "question": "When was 'Boysie Oakes' published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.558520495891571,
            "question": "Is John Gardner known for any specific writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5526055097579956,
            "question": "What nationality was John Gardner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4981766939163208,
            "question": "Can you name another book written by John Gardner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49059852957725525,
            "question": "What is the main plot of 'Boysie Oakes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42385008931159973,
            "question": "What type of work is 'Boysie Oakes'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38641634583473206,
            "question": "What genre does 'Boysie Oakes' likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3583293557167053,
            "question": "Has 'Boysie Oakes' been adapted into any other media?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29670432209968567,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in John Gardner's works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Gardner (British writer) wrote 'Boysie Oakes'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8192_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Boysie Oakes' been adapted into any other media?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8192_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'Boysie Oakes' likely belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8192_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is 'Boysie Oakes'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8192_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8192_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the required format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe context information and documents support this triple. According to the documents, John Gardner was a British spy and thriller novelist who created the character Boysie Oakes for his novel The Liquidator, which was published in 1964."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about John Gardner, an English author known for writing the Boysie Oakes series of novels. Therefore, the statement \"John Gardner (British writer) wrote 'Boysie Oakes'\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}